(punk rock music)
♪ Midnight to six man ♪
♪ For the first time from Jamaica ♪
♪ Dillinger and Leroy Smart ♪
♪ Delroy Wilson, your cool operator ♪
♪ Ken Boothe for UK pop reggae ♪
♪ With backing bands sound systems ♪
♪ If they've got anything to say ♪
♪ There's many black ears here to listen ♪
♪ But it was Four Tops all night ♪
♪ With encores from stage right ♪
♪ Charging from the bass
knives to the treble ♪
♪ But onstage they ain't
got no roots rock rebel ♪
♪ Onstage they ain't got
no roots rock rebel ♪
♪ Dress back jump back
this is a bluebeat attack ♪
♪ 'Cos it won't get you anywhere ♪
♪ Fooling with the gun ♪
♪ The British Army is waiting out there ♪
♪ An' it weighs fifteen hundred tons ♪
♪ White youth, black youth ♪
♪ Better find another solution ♪
♪ Why not phone up Robin Hood ♪
♪ And ask him for some
wealth distribution ♪
(instrumental)